Guide to the Dwight Hall, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1911-1980; Accession 1988-A-105
  - Summer Staff Listings, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 4198)
  - Summer Survey, 1973 (Box 143, Folder 4199)
  - Sunday Evening Meetings, 1917 (Box 144, Folder 4200)
  - Sunday Evening Meetings, 1925-1926 (Box 144, Folder 4201)
  - Survey Committee on Transition from High school to College, 1931-1932 (Box 144, Folder 4202)
  - Syrian Protestant College, 1916 (Box 144, Folder 4203)
  - Taft Hotel, 1974 (Box 144, Folder 4204)
  - Talks, 1939 (Box 144, Folder 4205)
  - Tapestry, 1955-1956 (Box 144, Folder 4206)
  - The Teacher Center, circa 1970's (Box 144, Folder 4207)
  - Telephone Toll Information, 1972 (Box 144, Folder 4208)
  - Temperance Movement, undated (Box 144, Folder 4209)
  - The Temple of Understanding, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 4210)
  - Tentative Bag: Summer Project, 1970 (Box 144, Folder 4211)
  - Thomas-for-President Club, 1932 (Box 144, Folder 4212)
  - Thomas, Norman: Radio Talks, 1940-1941 (Box 144, Folder 4213)
  - Thomas and Nelson Independent Committee, 1936 (Box 144, Folder 4214)
  - Tokyo, 1928 (Box 144, Folder 4215)
  - Torch Honor Society, 1950's (Box 144, Folder 4216)
  - Touché, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 4217)
  - Town Meetings, 1943-1944 (Box 144, Folder 4218)
  - Travancore and India Fund, 1953 (Box 144, Folder 4219)
  - Traveler's Aid, 1952 (Box 144, Folder 4220)
  - Traveler's Aid: Society of New Haven, 1956 (Box 144, Folder 4221)
  - Treasurer's Department, 1914-1921 (Box 144, Folder 4222)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1933-1934 (Box 144, Folder 4223)
  - Tribute to Marshall Bartholomew by Class of 1938, 1952-1953 (Box 144, Folder 4224)
  - Tribute to John G. Magee and Andrew R. Morehouse, 1953-1954 (Box 144, Folder 4225)
  - Trustees, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 4226)
  - Tucker, Luther: Articles, 1943 (Box 144, Folder 4227)
  - Tucker, Luther: Personal, 1941-1943 (Box 144, Folder 4228)
  - Tucker, Luther, 1945 (Box 144, Folder 4229)
  - Tutorial Proposal, 1968 (Box 144, Folder 4230)
  - Tutorial Program, 1963 (Box 144, Folder 4231)
  - Tutoring
    - 1965 (Box 144, Folder 4232)
    - 1968 (Box 144, Folder 4233)
  - Undergraduate Calendar, 1961-1962 (Box 145, Folder 4234)
  - Undergraduate Comments about Dwight Hall, 1917 (Box 145, Folder 4235)
  - Undergraduate Committee Minutes, 1933 (Box 145, Folder 4236)
  - Undergraduate Commission on Social and Economic Study, 1930 (Box 145, Folder 4237)
  - Undergraduate Members of Dwight Hall, Circa 1945 (Box 145, Folder 4238)
  - Union for Democratic Action, 1944 (Box 145, Folder 4239)
  - Union Missionary Training Institute, 1918 (Box 145, Folder 4240)
  - U.S.S.R. Exchange, 1960-1961 (Box 145, Folder 4241)
  - Union Theological Seminary
    - 1944 (Box 145, Folder 4242)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 145, Folder 4243)
    - Fund Raising, 1948 (Box 145, Folder 4244)
  - United Christian Youth Conference, 1937 (Box 145, Folder 4245)
  - United Church of Christ, after 1964 (Box 145, Folder 4246)
  - United Ministry in Higher Education, 1968-1969 (Box 145, Folder 4247)
  - United Ministry in Higher Education, 1972 (Box 145, Folder 4248)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1944-1946 (Box 145, Folder 4249)
  - United Student Christian Council
    - 1945 (Box 145, Folder 4250)
    - 1953 (Box 145, Folder 4251)
    - 1956 (Box 145, Folder 4252)
  - World Student Christian Federation Committee (WSCF), 1944-1945 (Box 145, Folder 4253)
    - Statements, 1945-1946 (Box 145, Folder 4254)
  - United Student Fellowship
    - 1956 (Box 145, Folder 4255)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 145, Folder 4256)
    - 1961 (Box 145, Folder 4257)
  - United Workers, 1921 (Box 145, Folder 4258)
  - United Workers' Boys' Club, 1917 (Box 145, Folder 4259)
  - United World Federations, 1955 (Box 145, Folder 4260)
  - University
    - 1926 (Box 145, Folder 4261)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 145, Folder 4262)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 145, Folder 4263)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 145, Folder 4264)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 145, Folder 4265)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 145, Folder 4266)
    - 1959 (Box 145, Folder 4267)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 145, Folder 4268)
    - 1969, 1973-1974 (Box 145, Folder 4269)
  - University Christian Association, undated (Box 146, Folder 4270)
  - University Christian Association, 1948-1949 (Box 146, Folder 4271)
  - University Christian Mission, 1937-1938 (Box 146, Folder 4272)
  - University Christian Missionary Committee, 1940 (Box 146, Folder 4273)
  - University Christian Movement, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 4274)
  - University Church Relationship, 1948 (Box 146, Folder 4275)
  - University Committee of Relations, 1934 (Box 146, Folder 4276)
  - University Council, undated (Box 146, Folder 4277)
  - University Memoranda, 1943-1944 (Box 146, Folder 4278)
  - University Memoranda, 1977 (Box 146, Folder 4279)
  - University Preachers, 1919-1920 (Box 146, Folder 4280)
  - University Preachers, 1929-1930 (Box 146, Folder 4281)
  - The Unschool of New Haven, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 4282)
  - Untitled Guest Lists, undated (Box 146, Folder 4283)
  - Upton close Cultural Expeditions, undated (Box 146, Folder 4284)
  - Urban, 1934 (Box 146, Folder 4285)
  - Urban 4-H, 1964-1965 (Box 146, Folder 4286)
  - V-12 Program (Yale International Club), 1943-1944 (Box 146, Folder 4287)
  - Verisus (YMCA), 1939-1940 (Box 146, Folder 4288)
  - Veterans, 1945-1946 (Box 146, Folder 4289 - 4290)
  - Vietnam Vets Against the War, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 4291)
  - Visit Norman Thomas, 1940-1941 (Box 146, Folder 4292)
  - Vista, 1969 (Box 146, Folder 4293)
  - Vista Recruitment, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 4294)
  - Vocation, 1960-1961 (Box 146, Folder 4295 - 4296)
  - Vocation Choices of Seniors, 1964 (Box 146, Folder 4297)
  - Volunteer Committee Copies, 1973-1974 (Box 146, Folder 4298)
  - Volunteer Manforce, 1974-1975 (Box 146, Folder 4299)
  - Volunteer Programs and Manpower, 1974 (Box 146, Folder 4300)
  - Volunteer Programs and Manpower, 1974 (Box 147, Folder 4301)
  - Volunteer Resources Library, 1974 (Box 147, Folder 4302)
  - Volunteer Services
    - 1961 (Box 147, Folder 4303)
    - 1962-1967 (Box 147, Folder 4304)
    - 1964 (Box 147, Folder 4305)
    - Council, undated (Box 147, Folder 4306)
    - Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 147, Folder 4307)
  - Voter Registration, 1972 (Box 147, Folder 4308)
  - Voter Registration Information, 1975 (Box 147, Folder 4309)
  - Voting Data
    - 1970 (Box 147, Folder 4310)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 147, Folder 4311)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 147, Folder 4312)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 147, Folder 4313)
  - Voting in the First Ward, 1973-1974 (Box 147, Folder 4314)
  - "Wanted: Professional Revolutionists": F. A. Henson, undated (Box 147, Folder 4315)
  - War Clippings: Wilder, Mrs. Charles J., 1943-1944 (Box 147, Folder 4316)
  - War Emergency Council, 1942-1944 (Box 147, Folder 4317 - 4318)
  - War Prisoners' Aid, 1944 (Box 147, Folder 4319)
  - War Prisoners' Aid Book Drive, 1943 (Box 147, Folder 4320)
  - War Prisoners' Aid Committee, 1940-1943 (Box 147, Folder 4321 - 4322)
  - War Relief, 1915? (Box 147, Folder 4323)
  - War Relief Campaign, 1940 (Box 147, Folder 4324)
  - War Time Responsibilities for "Resident Religious Agencies", 1942 (Box 147, Folder 4325)
  - War Work Council, 1917 (Box 147, Folder 4326)
  - War Work Fund
  - 1917-1918 (Box 147, Folder 4327 - 4328)
  - Weber, Vic, 1960-1961 (Box 148, Folder 4329)
  - Weddings, 1929, 1971 (Box 148, Folder 4330)
  - Wednesday-at-Five, 1930-1931 (Box 148, Folder 4331)
  - Wednesday Evening Series, 1926 (Box 148, Folder 4332)
  - Week of Prayer for Christian Unity, 1961 (Box 148, Folder 4333)
  - Welfare Moms, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 4334)
  - The Werdell Report, 1962 (Box 148, Folder 4335)
  - West Haven VA Companion Program, 1960's (Box 148, Folder 4336)
  - West Indies, 1946 (Box 148, Folder 4337)
  - Westminster Foundation at Yale (Presbyterians), 1956 (Box 148, Folder 4338)
  - Lt. White, John circa III Memorial, 1968-1969 (Box 148, Folder 4339)
  - Wider City Parish, 1960-1961 (Box 148, Folder 4340)
  - Wider City Parish, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 4341)
  - Williams College: Williamstown Institute of Human Relations, 1939 (Box 148, Folder 4342)
  - The Witness of Dr. Kagawa, 1945 (Box 148, Folder 4343)
  - Women at Yale, circa 1970's (Box 148, Folder 4344)
  - Women's Research Project, undated (Box 148, Folder 4345)
  - Wood, 1940's? (Box 148, Folder 4346)
  - Work Camps for America, 1940-1941 (Box 148, Folder 4347)
  - Work with the Elderly, 1970-1971 (Box 148, Folder 4348)
  - Work-Study Payroll Blanks, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 4349)
  - Work Study Program, 1973 (Box 148, Folder 4350)
  - World Conference of Christian Youth, Oslo, 1947 (Box 148, Folder 4351)
  - World Council of Churches, 1943 (Box 148, Folder 4352)
  - World Council of Churches, 1946 (Box 148, Folder 4353)
  - World Order, 1944 (Box 148, Folder 4354)
  - World Peace Program, 1944 (Box 148, Folder 4355)
  - World Relatedness Commission, undated (Box 148, Folder 4356)
  - World Relatedness Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 148, Folder 4357)
  - World Relations Committee:, 1950 (Box 148, Folder 4358)
  - World Student Christian Organization, 1942-1943 (Box 148, Folder 4359)
  - World Student Relief Fund, 1944-1945 (Box 148, Folder 4360 - 4361)
  - World Student Service Fund
    - 1941 (Box 148, Folder 4362)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 148, Folder 4363)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 148, Folder 4364)
    - 1943 (Box 149, Folder 4365)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 149, Folder 4366)
    - 1943-1945 (Box 149, Folder 4367)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 149, Folder 4368)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 149, Folder 4369)
    - Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 149, Folder 4370)
  - World University Service
    - 1955-1956 (Box 149, Folder 4371)
    - 1959 (Box 149, Folder 4372)
    - circa 1960's (Box 149, Folder 4373)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 149, Folder 4374)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 149, Folder 4375)
    - 1963 (Box 149, Folder 4376)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 149, Folder 4377)
  - World Youth Council, 1944 (Box 149, Folder 4378)
  - World's Student Christian Federation
    - 1928-1932 (Box 149, Folder 4379)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 149, Folder 4380)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 149, Folder 4381)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 149, Folder 4382)
    - 1942 (Box 149, Folder 4383)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 149, Folder 4384)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 149, Folder 4385)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 149, Folder 4386)
    - 1954 (Box 150, Folder 4387)
    - 1961 (Box 150, Folder 4388)
    - Bulletins, 1943-1944 (Box 150, Folder 4389)
    - Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 150, Folder 4390)
    - Council, 1943-1944 (Box 150, Folder 4391)
    - Finance Statements, 1945 (Box 150, Folder 4392)
    - Latin America, 1945 (Box 150, Folder 4393)
    - Leader's Meeting, 1945 (Box 150, Folder 4394)
    - Mexico, 1944-1945 (Box 150, Folder 4395)
    - News Sheet, 1937-1938 (Box 150, Folder 4396)
    - Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box 150, Folder 4397)
    - Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 150, Folder 4398)
    - Officers, 1945-1946 (Box 150, Folder 4399)
    - Officers and Finance, 1944-1945 (Box 150, Folder 4400)
    - Publicity, 1943 (Box 150, Folder 4401)
    - Relief and Reconstruction, 1942 (Box 150, Folder 4402)
    - Relief and Reconstruction, 1945-1946 (Box 150, Folder 4403)
    - Reports, 1939-1946 (Box 150, Folder 4404)
    - Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 150, Folder 4405)
    - Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 150, Folder 4406)
    - Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 150, Folder 4407)
    - South America, 1942-1943 (Box 150, Folder 4408)
    - South America, 1945-1946 (Box 151, Folder 4409)
    - Treasurer, 1945-1946 (Box 151, Folder 4410)
    - Treasurer: Latin America, 1945 (Box 151, Folder 4411)
  - World's Student Christian Federation: Banquet
    - 1930's (Box 151, Folder 4412)
    - 1934 (Box 151, Folder 4413)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 151, Folder 4414)
    - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 4415)
    - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 4416)
    - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 4417)
    - Invitation and Acceptances: New Haven People, 1935 (Box 151, Folder 4418)
    - Lists, 1935 (Box 151, Folder 4419)
    - Office Lists, undated (Box 151, Folder 4420)
    - Publicity, 1935 (Box 151, Folder 4421)
  - Worthington - Hooker Parent Teacher Association, 1953 (Box 151, Folder 4422)
  - Wright, Henry, Cottage, 1938-1939 (Box 151, Folder 4423)
  - Wright, Henry Memorial Cottage Dedication, undated (Box 151, Folder 4424)
  - Wright v. Montgomery, 1969-1973 (Box 151, Folder 4425)
  - Writing: Chales Swify, 1939 (Box 151, Folder 4426)
  - Writings, undated (Box 151, Folder 4427)
  - Writings, circa 1935-1936 (Box 151, Folder 4428)
  - XYZ, 1931 (Box 151, Folder 4429)
  - Yale Association, undated (Box 151, Folder 4430)
  - Yale at War, 1944 (Box 152, Folder 4431)
  - Yale Club, 1935-1936 (Box 152, Folder 4432)
  - Yale Club Fund Raising, 1969 (Box 152, Folder 4433)
  - Yale in China
    - Circa 1914-1920s (Box 152, Folder 4434)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 152, Folder 4435)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 152, Folder 4436)
    - 1928 (Box 152, Folder 4437)
    - 1930 (Box 152, Folder 4438)
    - 1931 (Box 152, Folder 4439)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 152, Folder 4440)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 152, Folder 4441)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 152, Folder 4442)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 152, Folder 4443)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 152, Folder 4444)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 152, Folder 4445)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 152, Folder 4446)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 152, Folder 4447)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 152, Folder 4448)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 152, Folder 4449)
    - 1942 (Box 153, Folder 4450)
    - 1943 (Box 153, Folder 4451)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 153, Folder 4452)
    - 1944 (Box 153, Folder 4453)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 153, Folder 4454)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 153, Folder 4455)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 153, Folder 4456)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 153, Folder 4457)
    - 1951-1953 (Box 153, Folder 4458 - 4459)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 153, Folder 4460)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 153, Folder 4461)
    - 1962 (Box 153, Folder 4462)
    - no date (Box 153, Folder 4463)
  - Yale in China: Requests for Donations, 1917 (Box 153, Folder 4464)
  - Yale Divinity School: Rev. Gaylord B. Noyce Work Study Program, 1970-1971 (Box 153, Folder 4465)
  - Yale in Jail, 1966 (Box 153, Folder 4466)
  - Yale Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 153, Folder 4467)
  - Young Men's Christian Association(YMCA)
    - 1944 (Box 153, Folder 4468)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 153, Folder 4469)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 153, Folder 4470)
    - 1962 (Box 154, Folder 4471)
    - New Haven, 1960-1961 (Box 154, Folder 4472)
    - Yale University, 1960-1965 (Box 154, Folder 4473)
    - 1967 (Box 154, Folder 4474)
    - Centennial, 1944-1945 (Box 154, Folder 4475 - 4476)
    - Connecticut, 1952-1953 (Box 154, Folder 4477)
    - Manuals and Employment, 1944 (Box 154, Folder 4478)
    - Minutes, 1948 (Box 154, Folder 4479)
    - National Council, 1942-1943 (Box 154, Folder 4480)
    - New Haven, 1944-1956 (Box 154, Folder 4481 - 4485)
    - Religious Emphasis Committee, 1944 (Box 154, Folder 4486)
    - Yale: Reports, 1926 (Box 154, Folder 4487)
  - Youth Committee Against War, 1939-1940 (Box 154, Folder 4488)
  - Youth Experimental Services, 1970-1977 (Box 154, Folder 4489)
  - Youth Fellowship Kit, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 4490)
  - Receipts of Donations, 1913-1917 (Box 155, Folder 4491)
  - Yale Battalion: Financial, 1916 (Box 155, Folder 4492 - 4493)
  - Miscellaneous, 1916 (Box 155, Folder 4494)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1916-1918 (Box 155, Folder 4495)
    - Financial
    - 1918 (Box 155, Folder 4496)
    - 1918 (Box 155, Folder 4497)
    - 1918 (Box 155, Folder 4498)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 155, Folder 4499)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 155, Folder 4500)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 155, Folder 4501)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 155, Folder 4502)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 155, Folder 4503)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 155, Folder 4504)
  - Financial, 1920-1921 (Box 156)
  - Bank Deposits, 1921 (Box 156, Folder 4505)
  - Financial, 1921-1931 (Box 156, Folder 4506)
  - Budget (Lists), 1925-1926 (Box 156, Folder 4507)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, [1925-1926?] (Box 156, Folder 4508)
  - Financial Letters, 1926 (Box 156, Folder 4509)
  - Budget, 1927-1928 (Box 156, Folder 4510)
  - Second National Bank, New Haven, 1930's-1970's (Box 156, Folder 4511)
  - Insurance, 1930's (Box 156, Folder 4512)
  - Budget (Box 156, Folder 4513)
  - Financial Letters, 1931 (Box 156, Folder 4514)
  - Financial, 1928-1934 (Box 156, Folder 4515)
  - Statements of Receipts and Disbursements: Yale YMCA, 1932-1937 (Box 156, Folder 4516)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1933 (Box 156, Folder 4517)
  - Student Volunteer Movement Financial Drive, 1933 (Box 156, Folder 4518)
  - Financial: Correspondence, 1934 (Box 156, Folder 4519)
  - Financial Letters, 1934 (Box 156, Folder 4520)
  - Financial Letters, 1935 (Box 156, Folder 4521)
  - Financial Letters, 1935 (Box 157, Folder 4522)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets, 1935 (Box 157, Folder 4523)
  - Investments, Stocks (Box 157, Folder 4524)
  - Balance Sheet for Fiscal Year, 1935 (Box 157, Folder 4525)
  - Income: Scranton and Co., 1935-1939 (Box 157, Folder 4526)
  - Financial, 1935-1943 (Box 157, Folder 4527)
  - Negro Work Financial Drive, 1936 (Box 157, Folder 4528)
  - Financial Letters, 1936-1937 (Box 157, Folder 4529)
  - Balance Sheet for Fiscal Year, 1936 (Box 157, Folder 4530)
  - Accounts, 1937-1938 (Box 157, Folder 4531)
  - Contributors and Deficit Givers, 1937-1939 (Box 157, Folder 4532)
  - New Haven Bank, 1938 (Box 157, Folder 4533)
  - Financial Campaign, 1938 (Box 157, Folder 4534)
  - Financial Statements, 1938 (Box 157, Folder 4535)
  - Financial Statements of the YMCA of Yale, 1938-1939 (Box 157, Folder 4536)
  - Yale University Budget
    - 1938-1939 (Box 157, Folder 4537)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 157, Folder 4538)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 157, Folder 4539)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 158, Folder 4540)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 158, Folder 4541)
  - Income and Expense Accounts, 1943-1952 (Box 158, Folder 4542 - 4543)
  - Second National Bank, New Haven, 1945-1947 (Box 158, Folder 4544 - 4545)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets
    - 1946-1951 (Box 158, Folder 4546)
    - 1946-1960 (Box 158, Folder 4547)
    - 1946-1960 (Box 159, Folder 4548 - 4549)
  - Sales and Use Tax, 1948-1951 (Box 159, Folder 4550)
  - Insurance Coverage of Yale YMCA at 406 Prospect Street, 1948-1952 (Box 159, Folder 4551)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1949-1950 (Box 159, Folder 4552)
  - U.S.N.S.A.: Bulletins, Constitutions, Financial, 1949-1950 (Box 159, Folder 4553)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets, 1949-1968 (Box 159, Folder 4554)
  - Insurance and Loan, 1950-1954 (Box 159, Folder 4555)
  - Snack Bar: Machine Sales Records, 1950-1954 (Box 159, Folder 4556)
  - Christian Association: Results of Audits and Operations, 1951-1953 (Box 159, Folder 4557)
  - Employee Records, 1951-1952 (Box 159, Folder 4558)
  - 10 Year Income and Expenses, 1952-1962 (Box 160, Folder 4559)
  - Employee Records, 1952-1958 (Box 160, Folder 4560 - 4561)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1954-1960 (Box 160, Folder 4562)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets, 1955-1967 (Box 160, Folder 4563 - 4564)
  - Christian Association: Results of Audits and Operations, 1955-1959 (Box 160, Folder 4565)
  - Employee Records, 1960's (Box 160, Folder 4566)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1960-1961 (Box 160, Folder 4567)
  - Record of Alumni Funding Drives, 1960-1970 (Box 160, Folder 4568)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1961-1962 (Box 160, Folder 4569)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets, 1961-1962 (Box 160, Folder 4570)
  - Choplin's Budget, 1962-1968 (Box 160, Folder 4571)
  - Endowment, 1962-1972 (Box 160, Folder 4572)
  - Endowment, 1962-1972 (Box 161, Folder 4573)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets, 1962-1969 (Box 161, Folder 4574)
  - Budgets, 1963-1969 (Box 161, Folder 4575)
  - Auditor's and Monthly Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 161, Folder 4576)
  - Legal Papers, 1963-1975 (Box 161, Folder 4577 - 4578)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1965-1969 (Box 161, Folder 4579)
  - Working Papers, 1966-1967 (Box 161, Folder 4580)
  - Journal and Ledger sheets, 1967-1971 (Box 161, Folder 4581)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1967-1971 (Box 161, Folder 4582)
  - State of Connecticut:, 1967-1972 (Box 162, Folder 4583 - 4584)
  - Work Papers for Taxes, 1968 (Box 162, Folder 4585)
  - Records of Finances, 1968-1971 (Box 162, Folder 4586)
  - Finances: Summer, 1969 (Box 162, Folder 4587)
  - Project Finances, 1969-1970 (Box 162, Folder 4588)
  - Payroll: Summer, 1970 (Box 162, Folder 4589)
  - Summer Proposal, 1970 (Box 162, Folder 4590)
  - Casual Employee File, 1970-1971 (Box 162, Folder 4591)
  - Tax Free Organization Form, 1970-1973 (Box 162, Folder 4592)
  - The Press Payroll, 1970-1974 (Box 162, Folder 4593)
  - Youth Crisis Defense Fund, 1970-1974 (Box 162, Folder 4594)
  - Financial Reports (Monthly Budgets), 1970-1976 (Box 162, Folder 4595)
  - Annual Funding Letters and Brochures, 1970-1978 (Box 163, Folder 4596)
  - Budget Use, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folder 4597)
  - Investment Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folder 4598)
  - University Christian Movement: Funding Letter, 1971 (Box 163, Folder 4599)
  - State of Connecticut: Report, 1971 (Box 163, Folder 4600)
  - Projected Budget: Dwight Hall Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folder 4601)
  - Executive Committee: Budgets, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folder 4602)
  - Annual Solicitation, 1971-1973 (Box 163, Folder 4603)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 4604)
  - Trustees Meeting, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 4605)
  - Entropy Funding, 1972-1973 (Box 163, Folder 4606)
  - Contributions of the Thorton Family Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 163, Folder 4607)
  - Funding Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 163, Folder 4608)
  - Alumni Solicitation, 1972-1973 (Box 163, Folder 4609)
  - Monthly Statements, 1973-1975 (Box 163, Folder 4610)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 4611)
  - Furniture Repairs, 1973 (Box 163, Folder 4612)
  - Thank You Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 163, Folder 4613)
  - City Plan: Budget Request (Box 164, Folder 4614)
  - Proxy Resolutions, 1974 April (Box 164, Folder 4615)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1974 (Box 164, Folder 4616 - 4617)
  - Benefit for ISC, 1974 (Box 164, Folder 4618)
  - Endowment Fund, Stewart Fund: Final Report, 1974 (Box 164, Folder 4619)
  - Stock Proxy, 1974-1975 (Box 164, Folder 4620)
  - Breakdown of Accounts: A.V.T. Copies, 1974-1975 (Box 164, Folder 4621)
  - Municipal Service, 1974-1975 (Box 164, Folder 4622)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1974-1976 (Box 164, Folder 4623)
  - Fundraising, 1974-1979 (Box 164, Folder 4624)
  - Computer: Alumni Records File maintenance Request, 1975 (Box 164, Folder 4625)
  - Insurance, 1976 (Box 164, Folder 4626)
  - Income Tax Information, 1976-1977 (Box 164, Folder 4627)
  - Proxies, 1976-1977 (Box 164, Folder 4628)
  - Advisory Board Finances, 1976-1977 (Box 164, Folder 4629)
  - White Collar: Wages, 1976-1979 (Box 165, Folder 4630)
  - Hurger Walk Contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 165, Folder 4631 - 4632)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 165, Folder 4633)
  - Grant Requests, undated (Box 165, Folder 4634)
  - Rooms for Rent, undated (Box 165, Folder 4635)
  - Journal and Ledger Sheets
    - 1942-1945 (Box 166, Folder 4636)
    - 1945-1948 (Box 166, Folder 4637)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 166, Folder 4638)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 166, Folder 4639)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 166, Folder 4640)
    - 1951-1959 (Box 166, Folder 4641)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 166, Folder 4642)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 4643)
    - 1959-1964 (Box 166, Folder 4644)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 166, Folder 4645)
    - 1969-1973 (Box 166, Folder 4646)
    - 1973-1977 (Box 166, Folder 4647)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1924-1951 (Box 167, Folder 4648)
  - Written Histories of Dwight Hall, 1920's-1940's (Box 167, Folder 4649)
  - Byers Hall, 1912-1927 (Box 167, Folder 4650)
  - Correspondence Concerning Removal of Yale YMCA from Dwight Hall
    - 1917 (Box 167, Folder 4651)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 167, Folder 4652)
    - 1924-1931 (Box 167, Folder 4653)
  - Conversion of Library to Dwight Hall, 1918-1930 (Box 167, Folder 4654)
  - Old Library, 1930-1931 (Box 167, Folder 4655 - 4658)